[Program ini termasuk tidak langsung
dan iklan virtual]
[Tempat persembunyian SVT Club]
[Anggota SVT Club berkumpul kembali
setelah seminggu]
- Kami kembali.
- Sudah lama.
- Kami di sini lagi.
Terakhir kali sulit
datang melalui pintu itu.
[Penting]
Hwan hyung! Hwan hyung!
[Kursi Hwan kosong]
Dia tidak di sini.
- Hwan hyung tidak ada di sini hari in.
- Aku tahu.
[Di mana Hwan?]
- Dia belum datang. - kapan dia datang ?
[Keributan]
Aku pikir dia menyiapkan sesuatu.
Ayolah! Jangan katakan padaku, Hwan hyung akan melakukannya
datang tanpa apa-apa!
[Penuh harapan]
Tidak mungkin!
[Pintu masuk besar SVT Club
minggu lalu]
[Menyenangkan hanya menonton]
[Mereka bertindak terlalu jauh karena tekanan]
Dimana saya?
Hwan hyung!
[Bagaimana Hwan bisa masuk?]
[Semua mata tertuju kepadanya]
Dia datang!
[Kenapa ini masalah besar?]
[Kenapa kita sangat bersemangat?]
aku gugup.
Guys!
[Bertepuk tangan keras]
[SEVENTEEN melakukan yang terbaik untuk bereaksi]
[Apa yang lucu?]
[Hanya melompat]
Guys!
[Malu]
[Tidak masalah. Kami merasakan hal yang sama]
[Sangat bijaksana] [Bersorak untuk Hwan]
Kim Hwan! Kim Hwan!`
[Terima kasih]
Tidak ada yang bisa dilakukan.
[Kritik profesional]
Saya meragukannya sampai dia berkata, "Guys".
[Anggun]
Tapi gerakan ini...
Gerakan ini sangat...
[Keluar dengan keringat dingin]
Saya tidak pernah merasa begitu tertekan di sebuah acara.
[Selamat datang di SVT Club]
- Kita semua ada disini sekaran, kan?
- iya.
[Kehadiran yang sempurna]
Sekarang, SVT Club.
Mari kita mulai.
- Apakah kalian memiliki minggu yang baik?
- iya.
Kami mencoba untuk mencapai keseimbangan
antara kerja dan hidup.
[Kata kunci minggu lalu, keseimbangan kehidupan kerja]
Keseimbangan kerja-hidup.
Saya menemukan hobi, pergi berbelanja,
dan menonton film.
[Itu yang baru]
- Saya membaca buku. - Kau membaca buku?
[Bingung]
[Matanya kehilangan fokus]
Anda tidak bekerja sama sekali selama seminggu terakhir?
[Tertangkap berbohong]
[Frustasi]
- Saya mencoba untuk menyeimbangkan. - Menyalurkan.
Setelah percakapan kami,
Saya terus berpikir tentang keseimbangan kehidupan kerja.
Betul. Aku Juga...
- Saya mencoba memanfaatkanya.
- Benar.
[Mengangguk]
Untuk penggunaan waktu anda yang paling berharga,
Saya yakin kalian telah bekerja keras untuk itu.
Kata kunci hari ini.
[Saat obrolan ringan]
Kunci yang dibesarkan
[Benarkah?] [Kapan?]
Sementara kami bicara.
- Buku? Shopping?
- Hobbi?
Bukankah itu hobbi secara keseluruhan?
Kata kunci kedua
yang panas di kalangan pemuda Saat ini.
Getting-satisfactioner.
Pengucapannya sedikit.
- Getting-satisfactioner.
- Pernahkah Anda mendengarnya sebelumnya?
Saya sudah sering mendengar dua huruf pertama.
[Berhati-hatilah dengan pengucapannya]
Dapatkan kepuasan.
[Tertawa keras]
Dalam situasi apa Anda mendengarnya?
[Spekulasi 1]
Ketika ada sesuatu yang lucu.
[Spekulasi 2]
- Ketika seseorang dalam suasana hati yang baik. - Menyenangkan.
Ketika ada sesuatu yang menyenangkan terjadi.
[Otak bekerja keras]
- Saat kamu beristirahat, saat aku sedang bekerja.
- Tepat sekali.
[Mereka yang beristirahat mendapatkan kepuasan]
Dapatkan kepuasan-er.
[[Apa itu artinya?]
"Mendapatkan kepuasan" diikuti oleh "er".
[Keterampilan deduksi bagus]
- Mereka yang istirahat. - Keterampilan deduksi yang bagus.
[Tee hee]
Mingyu mengangkatnya sebentar.
Pergi berbelanja.
[Aha!]
Kata itu terkait dengan belanja.
Ini ada hubungannya dengan belanja.
"Dapatkan" berarti membeli sesuatu.
Kepuasan berarti
Anda puas dengan sesuatu.
Get-satisfaction-er mengacu pada
seseorang yang mencari kepuasan.
Terlepas dari merek atau
efektivitas biaya,
jika Anda senang dengan pembelian,
itulah cara terbaik untuk konsumsi.
Itulah yang berarti kepuasan-er
[Apa arti yang mendalam]
Secara harfiah.
- Saya pikir kita akan berbicara tentang belanja.
- Belanja.
- Konsumsi apa yang membuat Anda senang?
Kita semua memiliki gaya belanja yang berbeda, bukan?
[Siapa SEVENTEEN minimalis?]
Pertama, siapa yang menghabiskan paling sedikit?
Ini disebut minimalis hari ini.
[Minimalis adalah seseorang yang mengurangi kepemilikan
paling sedikit dan nikmati hasil maksimal] [Me]
- Joshua?
- Shua benar-benar tidak membeli apapun.
[Diberikan]
Dia benar-benar tidak.
Saya belum pernah melihatnya
membeli apa pun.
Saya pergi ke window-shopping
umumnya.
Ketika saya melihat sesuatu,
Saya ragu.
[Dia tidak membeli setelah merenungkan]
Saya menyadari saya memiliki sesuatu yang serupa
jadi saya tidak perlu yang baru.
Biasanya itulah yang saya pikirkan.
Daripada menghabiskan uang untuk hal-hal semacam itu,
Saya lebih suka menghemat uang
untuk membeli apa yang saya inginkan nantinya.
- Itu sikap yang bagus.
- Saya tidak membeli banyak.
[Tercengang]
Hei!
Dia mengatakan itu dengan sengaja.
[Speechless] Anda selalu membawa
sesuatu yang baru ketika Anda pulang ke rumah.
- Setiap kali kamu kembali.
- Ini adalah pertama kalinya saya membeli sesuatu di luar negeri.
Dia adalah segalanya yang Anda inginkan
pembeli yang impuls.
Nyata!
Saya setuju!
- Saya menghitungnya.
- Benar, benar.
- Kerja bagus.
- Kamu akan membeli ini dan itu.
- Dan kamu merencanakannya.
- Iya.
- Anda baru saja menjalankan rencana Anda.
- Saya benar-benar membeli sesuatu yang ekstra.
[Secara sukarela mengatakan yang sebenarnya]
Itu berjalan seperti ini.
Ketika dia pergi untuk membeli sepasang sepatu baru,
dia membeli celana untuk cocok dengan sepatunya.
Beberapa orang melakukan itu.
Tapi kau tahu.
[Dilapisi gula]
Terlihat bagus untuk para penggemar.
- Benar.
- Pergi berbelanja untuk tujuan itu
tidak bisa disalahkan oleh orang lain.
Anda hanya menghabiskan sedikit lebih banyak daripada yang lain.
Anda berkomunikasi dengan penggemar Anda.
Kami tidak bisa menghakiminya.
[Saling membantu]
- Aku harus selalu terlihat baik. - Yakin.
- Benar.
- Kim Hwan.
[High five]
Anda bukan minimalis,
Anda lebih dari seorang binatang.
[Nice rhyming]
[Mencolek]
Apakah kamu suka itu?
[Respon yang kuat]
[Itu bagus]
[Bangga]
Luar biasa.
[Siapa No.1 yang mendapatkan kepuasan-er?]
Mari kita pilih siapa yang no. 1 get-satisfaction-er?
- Siapa yang akan kamu pilih?
- Saya akan memilih Vernon.
Saya pikir Dokyeom membeli paling banyak.
[Woozi berpendapat bahwa Dokyeom bukanlah yang satu ini]
Tapi kita tidak bisa memanggilnya mendapatkan kepuasan
- Dia tidak bisa puas.
- Karena dia tidak puas.
[Persaingan sengit]
[Dokyeom vs. Vernon]
- Saya pikir banyak nama akan disebutkan.
- OK.
Sebelum syuting,
kru produksi bertanya SEVENTEEN
siapa raja belanja.
- Raja belanja.
- Hasil adalah,
[Pemenang mendapat 7 suara dari 13]
Dengan tanah longsor, kami memiliki pemenang.
Ada pemenangnya.
Raja belanja adalah ?
[Drum roll]
Pemenangnya adalah
[As expected]
Dokyeom!
The king of shopping.
[Selamat]
- Biarkan saya berbagi beberapa cerita tentang Dokyeom.
- Baik.
Selalu ada kotak
di depan pintu rumah kami.
- Ya, saya dengar itu.
- Tapi ada kotak lain di hari berikutnya.
Dan hari berikutnya,
ada tumpukan kotak.
- Dia benar-benar membeli banyak.
- Mari kita dengar bagaimana perasaannya.
[Sangat tersebtuh]
Ini adalah kehormatan besar untuk dipilih
sebagai raja belanja.
[Tenang] - Saya akan meningkatkan upaya untuk membeli lebih banyak.
- Tidak, kamu tidak perlu.
[Bagaimana toko Dokyeom]
[Belanja online]
Saya ingin membeli ini.
Apa yang sedang kamu lakukan?
Belanja.
- Apakah Anda membeli sesuatu yang baru-baru ini?
- Baru-baru ini?
- Pakaian.
- Apakah kamu membeli pakaian?
Apakah kamu tidak memiliki kemeja yang sama?
[Baik...]
- Saya... - OK.
[Tidak ada pola yang sama di bawah matahari]
Ada perbedaan halus.
[Menyeringai]
-  Anda akan 100% ... - Tidak.
- buang salah satu dari mereka.
- Di lemari saya.
[Inspeksi] - Bagaimana kalau kita melihat lemari pakaianmu?
- Saya tidak punya benda ini.
[untuk menemukan pola yang sama]
Lanjutkan. Aku tidak punya yang asli.
Saya dapat menemukannya 100%.
[Lihat? Aku sudah bilang]
Aku benar-benar tidak.
Tidak, Anda memiliki begitu banyak kemeja bergaris.
[Apa lagi yang kamu sebut itu stripe?]
- Tapi... - Baiklah.
Saya tidak punya yang itu!
Anda bertindak terlalu jauh.
[Joshua si penyidik ​​menemukan kotak misterius]
- Aku ... - Apa ini?
[Brazen] - Apa ini!
- Saya membeli itu.
[Setumpuk kotak belum dibuka yang berharga]
Anda membeli terlalu banyak.
- Kamu bahkan tidak membukanya?
- Aku bahkan tidak mendapatkan setengah dari mereka.
Mari kita buka.
[Dokyeom dan Joshua Membuka kotak]
Apa itu?
[Kebenaran]
Saya harus membeli apa yang ingin saya beli.
[Bisakah Anda berhenti]
Tidak.
[Gembira]
Ini pembicara baru.
[Si AI yang sudah ditunggu-tunggu]
Mari ku tunjukkan.
[Asisten pembuka kotak]
- Buka Mereka. - Sebagian besar kotak dikirim untuk Anda.
Apakah Anda membeli kaus kaki?
[Mendapatkan kaos kaki hanya 1 klik saja]
Kaos kaki putih.
Apa ini?
Mantel?
[Mendapatkan mantel juga hanya 1 klik saja]
Ya, saya membeli mantel.
Apa ini?
Itu pelembab ruangan.
[Membersihkan kotak] [Khawatir]
Jangan membeli terlalu banyak untuk mendapatkan kesepakatan yang bagus.
[Tidak dapat mendengarnya melihat pembicara baru]
You'd end up buying too many stuff.
- Terhubung.
- Itu ada.
[Teman Dokyeom, AI speaker]
Panggil aku...
Kenakan musik yang bagus.
[Itu terlalu banyak untuk ditanyakan]
- Saya gagal menemukan lagu. - Benarkah?
- Haruskah kita memainkan daftar putar Anda?
- Lagu favoritmu.
[Sopan]
Silakan main "Pass By" oleh Nilo.
[Bingung]
- Wow! Luar biasa! - Bukan lagunya.
[Tentu saja]
- Ini bukan lagunya? - Tidak, bukan itu.
[Mengucapkan]
Silakan main "Pass By" oleh Nilo.
[Komunikasi AI-Dokyeom berhasil]
- Sangat menyenangkan.
- Itu benar?
[Bangga]
Kualitas audionya juga bagus.
[Dapatkan-kepuasan]
Itu pembelian yang bagus.
- Aku cinta kamu.
[Iron wall] - Saya seorang teman yang dapat dipercaya.
[Takjub]
Saya suka ini.
- Bukankah ini bagus?
- Sangat menyenangkan.
Mainkan "Falling For U" oleh SEVENTEEN.
[Sangat puas]
Anda membuat keputusan yang tepat.
- Saya tau? - Ini nyaman.
- Beginilah cara Anda menghilangkan stres.
[#Super puas #King belanja
# Get-satisfactioner] Ketika saya membeli sesuatu yang baru
Saya baik-baik saja.
[Dokyeom raja belanja,
dia benar-benar mendapatkan kepuasan]
Ketika saya pergi berbelanja offline,
Saya gagal dalam banyak kasus.
Jadi saya menikmati belanja online.
[Ketika pergi berbelanja dengan anggota]
Ketika saya melakukan pengiriman dengan beberapa anggota,
katakanlah saya memilih sesuatu yang saya suka.
Dan saya bertanya, "Bagaimana ini"?
Dan tanggapan mereka kurang antusias.
Anda tidak menyukai respon itu, bukan?
Itu yang saya tidak suka tentang itu..
Saya memilih sesuatu yang saya suka,
tetapi ketika orang lain tidak menyukainya,
- Itu tidak cocok untukmu.
- Lalu aku merasa kecewa.
Itu sebabnya saya lebih suka belanja online
untuk pergi berbelanja offline.
Saya melihat.
Jadi saya mengembangkan kebiasaan aneh.
Ketika saya mendapatkan paket
Saya membukanya secara diam-diam
dan coba secara diam-diam.
Jika saya tidak menyukainya,
Saya membuangnya segera.
[Tidak menyakiti harga dirinya]
Saya bummed.
- Jangan menangis.
- Saya mengerti Anda ingin diakui.
[Harap bersikap baik pada Dokyeom]
Saya takut berbelanja.
- Kenapa?
- Karena ... - Takut gagal.
Jika saya gagal, para anggota akan ...
[Astaga...]
- Saya mengerti perasaanmu. - Mereka menggangguku dengan kasar.
- Saya mengerti perasaanmu.
- Siapa yang melakukan itu?
Saya tidak akan mengungkapkan namanya.
[Tersangka biasa]
Tanggapan mereka
kurang antusias.
Since I'm afraid of it,
Saya tidak bisa membeli apa pun.
Saya hanya membeli barang-barang dasar.
[Membuat alasan] Itu bukan niat kami.
Kami hanya ingin Anda membeli sesuatu yang lebih baik.
- Kurasa kaulah orangnya.
- Kamu terlihat bersalah. - Itu jahat
[Hati nurani yang bersalah tidak membutuhkan penuduh]
Saya hanya berpikir dia bisa melakukannya dengan lebih baik.
Itu sebenarnya niat Anda.
[No soul]
Benar, benar. Karena alasan itu,
Saya akhirnya membeli lebih sedikit pakaian.
- Mari kita saling menghargai gaya satu sama lain.
- Tapi ...
[Menurut The8, raja mode]
Anda harus terus mencoba sesuatu yang baru.
Maka Anda dapat menemukan sesuatu
yang cocok untukmu.
- Kamu tidak boleh berhenti mencoba.
- Sesuatu yang mengekspresikan dirimu
- cocok untukmu yang terbaik.
- Benar.
Saya setuju dengan pola pikir Dokyeom.
Yang penting adalah jika Anda suka atau tidak.
- Kita tidak perlu mengikuti tren mode.
- Benar. Kami hanya harus membeli apa yang kami inginkan.
Itulah yang berarti kepuasan-kepuasan.
Ngomong-ngomong soal,
Apakah Anda memiliki kebiasaan membeli
yang tidak bisa didapatkan orang lain?
Saya tidak suka pergi keluar.
Saya tidak pandai belanja online.
[Kenapa belanja online sulit?]
Karena saya di bisnis musik,
banyak orang di sekitarku
dalam bisnis mode.
Jadi saya bertanya kepada mereka.
Saya memberi tahu mereka gaya seperti apa yang saya inginkan.
Lalu mereka mendapatkannya untuk saya
dan saya membayar kepada mereka.
- Itu pola saya.
- Kemudian Anda berbagi selera Anda secara detail?
Karena mereka ahli dalam mode
dan mereka tahu ukuran saya.
[Tingkat kegagalan 0,001%]
Saya hampir gagal.
[Bagaimana toko Woozi]
[Belanja dengan proxy]
[Humming]
[Kamar Woozi dan Mingyu]
Akankah manajer kami mengangkat telepon?
Dia keluar untuk jadwal Boo-Seok-Soon.
[Vernon datang]
Ruangan ini luar biasa.
[Pertama kali datang ke kamar setelah pindah]
Hai saudaraku.
- Bisakah saya membukanya?
- Tunggu sebentar. Apa yang sedang kamu lakukan?
[Buka pintunya]
Kapan Anda pergi ke
membangun perusahaan baru?
[Kenapa dia naik ke sana?]
Sekitar 3 atau 4 jam?
Saya sudah memesan beberapa pakaian ke gedung.
Akan ada paket untuk saya.
Tolong diperiksa.
- Baiklah. - Terima kasih.
- Aku akan memberitahu Anda.
BAIK. Terima kasih.
[Pemilik kamar kembali]
Apa yang kamu lakukan?
[Orang asing mengambil alih tempat tidur Mingyu]
Saya memesan pakaian.
I called our manager
to check the packages for me.
- Dia mengangkat teleponnya selama
Jadwal Boo-Seok-Soon. - Apa yang Anda beli?
Itu adalah sesuatu yang Jaehoon dapatkan untukku.
Musim gugur ONEHUNNNIT.
Dia mengatakan ada pendatang baru.
Saya mengatakan kepadanya untuk mendapatkan segalanya untuk saya.
- Hitung saya.
- Keluar dari biru?
Akan ada pakaian ekstra
dalam paket saya.
Saya tidak hanya meminta milik saya.
- Saya memintanya untuk membeli semuanya.
- Benarkah?
- Akan ada banyak.
- Saya tidak membeli apa pun sendiri.
[Pertama kali mengungkap lemari pakaiannya]
Saya mendapatkan sebagian besar dari mereka
dari teman-teman saya di dunia fashion.
Apakah itu cocok?
[Yakin]
Ya.
[Pro No. 1 belanja oleh proxy]
Karena mereka semua tahu
ukuran saya sudah.
Siapa yang tahu ukuran saya?
[Pro No. 2 belanja oleh proxy]
- Mereka bahkan memperbaiki pakaian untukku. - Benarkah?
Itu bagus.
Kenapa mereka mau belanja untukmu?
[Keren abis]
Karena kita sudah dekat.
- Karena kamu sudah dekat.
- Tentu saja.
- Kenapa kamu di tempat tidurku?
- Karena itu sangat nyaman.
[Mingyu memegang kamera]
- Apa itu? - Mereka mirip.
Karena saya bertanya pada teman-teman saya
untuk berbelanja untukku,
Saya memiliki pakaian yang serupa
[Mereka semua hitam]
- Ini membentang.
- Benar
- Hei, turunlah.
- Karena aku sering mencuci mereka.
[Dengan siapa saya berbicara...]
- Ini tempat tidurku. - Mereka dicuci berkali-kali.
Saya ingin Anda turun
dari tempat tidurku.
Ini seperti memasukkan tembakan lemari.
[Saklar kamera Mingyu
subyek sangat cepat]
- Kamar kami luar biasa.
- Woozi! Woozi!
[Bersemangat Mingyu sang sutradara]
Mengakhiri ucapan, silakan. [
[Kesalahan di hadapan umum]
Belanja dengan proxy luar biasa.
[Syuting lagi]
Kamu tahu apa?
- Apa?
- Untuk perawatan kulit ...
[Mingyu adegan penutup sutradara]
Dapatkah Anda melihat orang-orang di sana?
Lemari bajuku.
- Belanja?
- Oleh teman.
[2018 SEVENTEEN kata kunci]
[Perawatan #Skin untuk pelembab] [#My wardrobe]
[#Belanja oleh teman] [#Belanja oleh proxy]
Ini seperti merek sekarang.
Di samping itu,
apakah ada di antara kalian
harus melihatnya sendiri
[Hoshi, S.Coups]
sebelum kamu membeli sesuatu
[Joshua, The8]
Saya harus mencobanya.
- Anda mencobanya?
- Iya nih. - Anda mencobanya.
- Dan kamu pergi berbelanja?
- Iya nih.
Saya tidak mencobanya.
Saya hanya memutuskan apa yang harus dibeli di muka.
[Buat daftar belanja dan ambil. Tamat]
Lalu saya membeli barang itu dan pulang.
- Dan kau?
- Saya mengikuti naluri saya.
Pakaian dan karakter Anda
berjalan dengan baik bersama hari ini.
[Penghibur profesional]
Karena pakaianmu
Anda tampak seperti Anda mengikuti
garis saya.
[Keren]
- Ikuti nalarku. - Anda mengikuti naluri Anda.
Selama tur Osaka Anda,
- Anda butuh waktu untuk berbelanja.
- Iya.
- Siapa yang pergi belanja bersama?
- Pada waktu itu,
[Pasangan belanja Osaka, The8, Wonwoo, Mingyu]
Pada waktu itu, aku, The8 ...
[Vernon]
- Empat dari kami. - Empat dari kamu? - Iya.
[Item permata apa yang mereka dapatkan?]
[Jalan Jeruk,
distrik perbelanjaan modis di Osaka]
[Tim belanja tim kerja]
[Wonwoo, Vernon] [Mingyu, The8]
Sudah 3 tahun
sejak kami pergi berbelanja bersama.
Tidak, belum lama ini.
[Teman belanja hari ini, Wonwoo dan Vernon]
- Tidak lama? - Kami pergi berbelanja bersama.
[Visual luar biasa]
- Kapan itu? - Rodeo ...
- Benar, benar.
- Kami naik taksi dan pergi ke Garosu-gil. - Iya.
Kemana kita harus pergi?
Saya suka toko semacam itu.
Tanpa merek.
[Bagaimana Wonwoo shop] [Beli jika itu bagus]
Saya tidak peduli dengan merek.
Sangat lucu.
Ketika saya masih kecil,
- Apa?
- Saya ingin memakai pakaian itu.
Tapi orang tuaku menangkapku
hanya gaya biasa.
- Saya ingin sesuatu yang mencolok dan penuh warna.
- Benar.
- Itu seperti...
- Ya, itu terjadi ketika kamu masih kecil.
[Fashionista SEVENTEEN The8 sedang berbelanja
dengan Mingyu] Ke mana kita harus pergi?
[Garis klise]
Apakah ada tempat yang bagus?
[Melihat sekeliling]
Aku tahu.
Saya tidak dapat menemukan apa pun
yang menarik perhatian saya.
Haruskah kita mengambil gambar
di sana?
[Belanja bukan prioritas] [Tempat bagus untuk foto]
- Bolehkah kita? - Disana.
[Mingyu model]
Tapi sedikit ...
[Fotografer dan model alami]
Seperti dalam peragaan busana?
Peragaan busana...
[Fotografi fesyen jalanan]
[Kemistri hebat]
Cukup.
[Senang kamu bersenang-senang]
Daripada berbelanja,
[Semuanya baik]
- kami lebih ... - Sepertinya kami datang untuk mengambil gambar.
[Tertarik]
Tempat itu terlihat bagus.
Apa mereknya?
[Memasuki toko sebelum mereka mengetahuinya]
Ayo pergi.
[Mingyu dan The8 memilih toko vintage]
Beli dan jual.
- Beli dan jual.
- Saya suka ini.
[Pink adalah cara untuk pergi]
- Apa itu? - Ini akan cocok dengan celana, kan?
Jenis gaya retro,
Kamu tahu apa maksudku?
Itu celanaku.
Anda mencoret-coret mereka.
[Sebelumnya celana Mingyu]
Jika Anda tidak membelinya ...
- I'll throw it away.
- I bought those pants
Saya membuat celana lebih ramping.
- dan Anda mencoret-coret mereka.
- Jadi kamu bersyukur, bukan?
[Belanja Fashionista]
[Ini terlihat cukup bagus]
- Berapa harganya?
- Sebuah baju hangat. 1,4 juta won.
Oh
Ini sandal yang cukup bagus.
Mereka. Berapa harganya?
Itu terlalu mahal.
[Sandal merek mewah.
Terlalu mahal]
700.000 won untuk sandal.
Saya akan membeli jika saya memiliki saku yang dalam.
Mengapa mereka semua kecil?
[Kecewa Mingyu]
Saya tidak bisa membeli apa pun karena terlalu mahal.
Haruskah kita mencobanya?
Jadi kita mengerti itu.
[Akan lebih baik untuk mencobanya]
Terlalu kecil!
[Super slim fit]
- Ini terlalu kecil. - Ini kecil.
- Pakaiannya Tidak pas untukku.
- Karena kamu menjadi lebih besar.
Aku sangat kecewa.
Saya suka itu!
[Wonwoo dan Vernon]
Tempat ini terlihat bagus.
[Toko topi]
Begitu banyak hal untuk dilihat.
Haruskah kita masuk?
Saya ingin mendapatkan topi.
- Sebuah topi?
- Saya ingin melihatnya. - Baiklah.
[Wonwoo dan Vernon memilih
toko topi]
Saya akan cepat.
[Vernon langsung]
Apakah kamu punya sesuatu
kamu inginkan? Yang itu bagus.
- Yang ini dan ...
- Ini akan sempurna untuk lemari pakaianmu.
[Membeli dengan warna]
[Topi yang sama dengan warna kuning]
Saya hanya bisa memakai ini.
[Penghargaan manis Wonwoo]
Kelihatan bagus.
-  Apakah kamu akan membelinya?
- Ya Saya suka mereka.
Yang ini bagus.
Tunggu sebentar.
Saya baru saja melihat topi saya.
Yang mana?
[Vernon, penggemar Star Wars yang sangat besar]
- yang itu? - Darth Vader. - Bagus.
[Topi kolaborasi Star Wars]
Itu bukan lelucon. Ingin saya mengambilnya dari rak?
[Menggunakan kamera]
[Biarkan aku mengambilnya untukmu]
[Kamera diletakkan]
[Senang]
Kolaborasi Star Wars.
- Sangat lucu. - Saya suka ini.
[Dibeli dengan dua topi]
Saya ingin topi kuning ini dan Star Wars satu.
[Tergoda]
Tunggu sebentar. Haruskah saya membeli yang putih?
[Belanja penuh gairah Vernon]
Anda sedang berpikir keras.
[1 detik sudah cukup]
Anda ingin melihat yang putih?
Anda adalah pembeli yang impulsif.
Saya pikir saya.
[Akulah yang mendapatkan kepuasan]
- Lalu ... - Darth Vader.
[Sementara itu,
Wonwoo masih berpikir]
[Haruskah saya mencobanya?]
[Smurf Wonwoo]
Topi itu terlihat bagus untukmu.
Saya harus memikirkannya.
[Secara tidak sengaja mencocokkan topi]
Bukankah ini bagus?
Anda memilih mereka bertiga.
- Saya akan mendapatkan dua ini.
- Ketiga ini.
- Tiga? - Iya nih.
- BAIK. Terima kasih. Maaf.
Tidak untuk dijual.
- Ini Tidak dijual?
- Ini bukan untuk dijual.
[Staf menjelaskan sesuatu]
-  Apa? Apa yang salah?
- Ini bukan untuk dijual.
[Kebenaran yang mengejutkan]
- Ini bukan untuk dijual? - Ini untuk pameran.
[Untuk pameran]
[Mereka memilih topi hanya untuk pameran]
XL.
- Saya harus membeli yang lain.
- Anda Tidak akan membeli topi?
[Konsumen yang hati-hati Wonwoo]
Saya suka detailnya.
Aku tahu! Saya sangat menyukainya.
[Topi persis seperti gaya mereka]
Sangat buruk.
Kolaborasi Darth Vader.
[Mingyu dan The8 lupa tentang belanja]
Berdiri di tengah.
BAIK.
[Mereka menjadi fotografi fashion jalanan]
Ini seperti kami datang untuk berfoto
bukan untuk belanja.
[Tepat pada]
Betul!
[Modelnya dalam fotografi]
[Dan fotografer The8]
Tunggu sebentar.
[Malu]
Apakah kamu tidak ingin ada foto?
Saya akan mengambil foto Anda.
[Keren]
Tidak, saya baik-baik saja.
Ini sangat keren.
Duduklah di sana.
[Duo belanja yang menakjubkan,
Mingyu dan The8]
[Sangat bagus]
Itu terlihat sangat bagus.
Kita bisa melakukan pemotretan bersama.
[Menawarkan kemitraan]
Kami mengambil foto masing-masing.
Pemotretan mode?
[Apakah itu SEVENTEEN?]
[Apakah dompet Anda baik-baik saja?]
Apakah kamu membeli sesuatu?
Dia memotret lagi.
[Observasi yang tajam]
Saya melihat Anda membeli topi.
[Memamerkan topi barunya]
- Kami membeli 3 topi. - Dalam desain yang sama?
- Ya, dalam warna berbeda.
- Kami baru saja mengambil foto. - Benarkah?
[Kisah lengkap belanja Osaka mereka akan
terungkap di NAVER TV] Kami baru saja membicarakannya.
[VLive Ver] Klub Mnet E02 SVT
- ♥ Ruo Xi ♥ -
Dalam hal ini,
dan The8 mungkin serupa.
Saya tidak bisa membeli sesuatu sekaligus
meskipun saya menyukainya.
[Benar] - Itu sifatmu.
- Ya, di toko di sekitar sini
[Gaya belanja hati-hati Mingyu]
Saya menemukan sesuatu yang saya suka.
Tapi saya harus memikirkannya lebih jauh
ketika saya membeli barang.
Saya membeli sesuatu yang saya beli sebelumnya.
Since we went shopping in Japan.
Once you buy something
- it's hard to go back to the store.
- Right.
It's not easy.
[Taking pictures was just an excuse]
So I couldn't buy anything easily.
- I can't get a refund.
- Right.
You bought the same hats
in three colors.
It's quite unique, I guess.
[Something on Hoshi's head caught his eyes]
For example...
[Hoshi's eye-catching beret]
I'm sorry.
Let's say he buys zebra pattern
on top of this one.
- Dalmatian.
- and dalmatian pattern.
[Not my style]
It's too unique of a style.
[Crack up]
That was a wrong example.
[Vernon's cart]
- White, black, yellow. - Black and yellow.
Do you all understand
Vernon's shopping style?
[Fashionista]
I get it.
[Respect his taste]
I do get it, though I wouldn't do the same.
- But I understand.
- As for hats,
[Vernon's style, buying different colors]
When you have it in different colors,
it's easy to match with your clothes.
Yeah, you can find your own style.
- Osaka... - Never mind.
- Go ahead.
[Seungkwan seems like he has something to say]
- Never mind. - Go ahead.
- Go ahead.
- You don't need to be too cautious. - Yes.
Since this is a reality show...
[What is going on?]
[So cool]
Can I go to the bathroom?
[Burst out laughing]
[Respect]
While you guys are talking...
- You may go.
- I didn't go shopping in Osaka.
You didn't go shopping.
[Laughing so hard]
I'll be back quickly.
Should I go this way...
- What is he doing?
- He's really something.
It's all right. It's real.
It's all right. No big deal.
Let's talk while he's gone.
[Seungkwan must have endured a lot]
Imagine how long he's been waiting.
[SVT Club gathered together after a week]
The zebra pattern...
[Everyone is having fun]
[Except me]
[Putting the moments
where he can't smile behind]
Can I go to the bathroom?
When I was in junior high
and high school,
[Michael Jordan]
You know the best basketball player of all time.
- That brand.
- I was such a huge fan of his.
I wanted to buy sneakers.
But I didn't have money.
- It was all the rage when I was in junior high.
- So...
As I started making money
I buy those sneakers.
As I can afford it now,
I keep buying those sneakers like crazy.
I found myself collecting them.
In my place...
I think I have 40 pairs.
That's amazing.
I'm curious what item you collect,
if any.
- First...
- In my case, you might be find it surprising.
- I love wine.
- Wine? - Yes.
[Wine mate Mingyu and The8]
- Right. - The8 and I enjoy wine together.
[Taken aback] - Lighting a candle.
- With a candle? Just you two?
[Playing some jazz tune]
And we play music.
I enjoy the atmosphere.
When we lived in the dorm,
when I entered The8 and Mingyu's room,
[When you entered our room?]
Then I immediately stepped back,
saying, "Here we go again".
[Agree]
The other members might not get it.
When we finish a wine bottle,
we rinse it and collect them.
How many bottles did you collect?
We had about 20 bottles.
We threw them away
while moving.
[I'm a guy who collects wine bottles]
Anything else you guys collect?
[Looking around]
[I'll pass]
[No one else?]
[I guess there's no one]
I collect something.
[What is it?]
There's someone.
[Shy]
I...
- collect my video clips.
- Seriously!
- My...
- Seriously, man.
- The video clips I monitored...
- You collect them?
- In the album. - You can organize.
- I can organize them.
I save all of them in the album.
- Even when I can't use data.
- It's in your album.
Even in the airplane mode.
I always monitor them 24/7.
[That's really amazing]
I look into it in detail.
[Passionate youngest]
I want to be more perfect.
So I want to go for it.
[Respect]
When the members pass by,
for example Dokyeom...
Every time I monitor the videos,
Dokyeom always passes by.
He says, "Are you monitoring again"?
[Perfect timing] [The one who passes by
whenever he monitors] I say, "Yes".
If I run into him 5 times a day,
every time, he is monitoring something.
We do monitor a lot.
[The youngest on top] [So passionate]
[Shy] He's amazing.
When you collect something,
one by one
- you can be reminded of the good old times.
- Right.
- You remember it. - That makes sense.
- When you watch those videos in the past,
- you can remember the good old times.
- So I sometimes watch old videos.
So Hoshi, you collect something, right?
I've been collecting money
these days.
[Straight face]
I've been collecting money.
Hey...
Wait a moment.
[1 minute ago] [Mingyu!] [What?]
I save them
[Ask me a question]
And I watch them.
[I can make it fun]
And I look into it
in detail.
[OK. Got it]
I want to be more perfect.
[Seeking the timing]
So I want to go for it.
- I've been collecting money.
- You two planned this, right?
[Dumbfounded]
You wanted me to ask a question!
You wanted me to ask a question.
[Talking down, out of betrayal]
Is that what you've got?
[Go, Hoshi!]
How about Jun?
Do you collect anything?
- I collect pictures.
- Pictures?
The pictures we share
in the group chat room.
- I collect funny pictures.
- Pictures of us?
That's dangerous.
We use our funny pictures
instead of emoticons.
- We use it as emoji.
In our group chat room,
when someone starts sharing
embarrassing pictures,
we go crazy.
[Group chat room hell]
There are 13 people...
It's nothing risky.
I collect cute ones
and heart-warming pictures
in the album.
But we end up sharing
our almost nude pictures at the end.
[Fail to sugar-coat]
- It gets crazy. - It's supposed to be
that way to be fun. - It's fun.
We get competitive.
There are hundreds of messages
in just a few minutes.
[Is it real?]
It's shocking. Oh my! So many messages.
- Everyone jumps into it.
- Yeah.
I save funny photos.
[Jun's fingers have been busy to save them]
I mean...
When you look at them
after many years from now,
[Precious memories build up that way]
rather than nice-looking selfie,
- silly pictures remain in our memories longer.
- Right.
And we'd want to save them.
We didn't get to reveal our
funny pictures for the sake of our image.
It'd be nice to share our
funny pictures in a fan meeting event.
[Huh? For real?]
I thought about it.
We could show our funny pictures
on the huge LED screen.
[Surprisingly positive response]
- What is happening in the picture. - Sounds good.
I've thought about it.
[Here they are]
Among the items you bought recently,
something you're very satisfied with.
It's called "it" item.
- I'm sure you have one.
- Get-satisfactioner.
I heard you'll reveal your "it" item.
- Right.
- I heard you brought it here.
[To be continued]
[What is your "it" item?]
It's "it" item as they call it.
- I'm sure you have one.
- Get-satisfactioner.
I heard you'll reveal your "it" item today.
I heard you brought it here.
[Taking out something]
[Various "it" items]
There are so many kinds.
[Wearing his "it" item] [Earphone mania Dokyeom]
Please introduce your "it" item.
What is yours, Dokyeom?
Earphones?
[He's into audio gears]
I love earphones.
In-ear earphones.
I'm into audio gears,
though I don't know well.
I try new earphones.
[I get it] - Based on your sense.
- I try to figure out the difference.
[Music is my life]
[Get-satisfactioner]
[Look at his acting]
[I'm serious] I try to figure it out.
And as for the in-ear I use on a stage.
I had one,
and I bought another one.
I alternate them for each stage.
I can't go into too much detail.
Anyways, my "it" item is earphones.
I've been looking for earphones.
[Seriously?]
You'll get another one? You already have a lot.
[1st reason to buy, audio quality]
Every earphone delivers different audio quality.
[2nd reason]
It feels different.
You should stop buying.
I've been looking for new earphones.
This one has this Bluetooth thing.
But this one doesn't have
a cable at all.
I can just wear them in my ears.
You even watch the review video.
I have to check out the review.
- I should watch it first.
- Isn't it unnecessary?
No.
[4th reason to buy, fashion]
I wear different earphones
for different outfits.
[5th reason to buy, hobby]
Collecting earphones is kind of my...
It's my hobby.
I'm so happy when I buy audio gears.
[Sidetracked] - Let's watch speakers now.
- You're No. 1 in buying stuff.
[The king of shopping, Dokyeom]
I'm glad I'm No. 1.
You're glad you're No. 1?
It's No. 1 anyway.
Isn't this pretty?
[You should feel it]
Look how the speaker and earphones look.
[I don't get it]
[Product review videos]
You should stop watching these.
If you stop watching
these review videos,
- you might be able to cut back on spending.
- It's pretty.
[He's not listening]
It's so pretty.
Are you wearing your favorite "it" item?
These are very comfortable.
This hook is nice.
When you wear earphones,
- it falls off easily.
- It does. But when I wear it during workout,
[See?]
it hardly falls off.
[So stable]
I mean...
It's like home shopping channel.
I bought these on the plane.
[Duty free chance]
On the plane. And it was on sale.
- So it's your favorite among many other ones?
- Yes.
[They use the same earphones]
- I'm glad to hear that. I bought that. - Really?
[Relieved]
- I have the same earphones. - It's nice.
So I asked if an earphone geek
is really satisfied with it.
[Earphone geek's choice]
[Clip-on earphone
bought on the plane]
[Seungkwan's "it" item]
What did you bring, Seungkwan?
It's a massage machine.
[Are you an actress?] I've never seen
someone carrying that other than an actress.
Really?
I'm proud.
My face gets puffy so easily.
It was my big concern.
The members wondered
why I would need this.
[My way] [He bought it despite their jeers]
They said, "You bought some strange stuff".
[This is so special]
If I push the button, it vibrates.
Does that thing roll?
Let him try it.
I'll give you a massage, Hwan.
[Seungkwan's home shopping]
- It's like home shopping channel. - This is...
When you're tired in the morning
and you need to wake up.
[Right up my alley]
This is nice. The vibration is great.
[How is it?]
And then...
- This is.
- Are you willing to buy it?
- How much is it? 39,800 won?
- Your sides...
[The salesperson gives a massage]
- Nice. - On your sides
and your back.
Also your ears.
[Huh? Ears?]
Why ears?
[Urgent]
[Are you okay, Hwan?]
- He doesn't look okay. - Everyone.
I'd like to give this information
to SVT Club viewers.
All the nerves of our body
are connected to our ears.
If you have a back pain,
your ears would hurt.
- We can find out if you're healthy or not.
- How much is it?
[Leave my ears alone]
Argh!
- You're not healthy.
- That was...
I guess it's the first time
for someone to hold my ear, besides teachers.
[No comparison]
Teachers pull your ears to punish.
But I rubbed it, like a massage.
[Blaming eyes]
You need to massage your ears.
[Making a good excuse]
- That's right. - Really.
You bought something
that matches you well.
[Likely to buy]
- How much? - 80% off.
- So nice.
- 80%?
[So I bought it]
[Next one to reveal his it-item?]
- What's the next? - Yes.
[Wonwoo's track suit]
- Wonwoo? - This is my track suit.
I love comfortable clothes.
[Track suits account for 80% of his clothes]
I wear track suits on my way to the airport.
We were ad models of this brand.
- Oh.
- So when we were models,
[Track suits received from the advertiser]
I brought the track suit we received.
[Blinking]
[No words to say]
[Mingyu is laughing so hard]
He found no words to say.
Is it an "It" item?
[Laughing out loud]
[Wonwoo feels nervous]
[Nobody understands Wonwoo]
Please show us how it looks on you.
You still have a chance.
[Not knowing where to put his hands]
Can I say something?
[Hang on]
This is mine.
[Rented it item] [The biggest fraud]
It's mine.
He lost his.
So I let him use this.
[Listen to me]
Let me tell you what happened.
[Explaining]
I wanted to brought a track suit.
[But it's gone]
- I lost these.  - When we moved out.
When we moved out,
I lost these.
Thank you for your
bold decision.
But an "It" item varies per person
depending on how you cherish it.
It's something that holds
a great value to yourself.
[Members start laughing with
MC's comment] He's summarizing.
[You got me]
Honestly,
I think I should give
an ear massage to him again.
Even though you can't understand...
I can't understand it.
Even if you wonder why?
[If it's valuable to you,
it's "It" item for satisfaction!]
If you think it's valuable,
that's a good item for you.
[I did my best to sugarcoat]
[As long as Wonwoo likes it,
he's the get-satisfactioner!]
[My turn]
Who's next?
[Cutie Vernon] [He was waiting]
- Vernon's enthusiastic. - Well,
[Starting bragging about]
- Awesome. - If you download this app,
you can control this robot.
[A Japanese shopping mall]
It consists of 8 floors and the basement.
It's really big,
like the Dongdaemun mall in Korea.
[Four members start shopping]
Will you buy a puzzle?
- Wow!
- Isn't it something you like?
- It's not my best favorite thing.
[Mingyu & The8 brothers like these]
It's to scratch.
It's the pastel painting.
[Objects related to drawing and painting]
- I need to paint over it. - This is nice.
[Ignoring]
- Buy me one! - Sorry?
If this were in Korea,
I would buy so many things.
[From Japan to Korea]
It will be hard to bring things to Korea.
[Looking around]
Is this skin the material
of hand-made goods?
[Correct]
Wow.
[Hand-made products]
Why can't I take my eyes off them?
[Mingyu's how to shop]
If someone gives this to me,
[Careful shopper who
thinks twice before buying]
I think I can make something.
That's so nice.
There's nothing I really want to buy.
[Wonwoo and Vernon]
[DIY package for cheering fans]
This is a package to
decorate fans to cheer.
[Curious]
Is this a real food?
[Various range of products]
- I guess so. - Is this real?
Emergency food for a disaster.
Awesome.
[Amazed by the shop]
Wow! Is this a miniature figure?
[Cute] [Like a wow-bot]
Is this a plastic figure? Wow!
Isn't it a chair for fishing?
[Amazed]
There's a section for hands-on experiences.
[Humming]
[Wonwoo's pure reactions]
Wow! If I'm good at this,
I want to do this.
[Recommending a hobby]
This would be a nice hobby.
What's this? Fragrance?
[Wonwoo's preference]
- This is pretty.
- I thought about doing this.
[Wonwoo keeps talking to himself]
So pretty. It'd be nice if I do it later.
I like home decoration.
- Isn't it amazing?
- Do you like tea?
Me? Thank you.
[Sipping a cup of tea]
May I buy one?
[Purchasing one]
May I buy this?
I like things that I've
never done when I was young.
[A whole new world to Wonwoo]
I've never had a chance like this.
Experiences...
[Wonwoo's how to shop
- Buy everything in his basket]
I hope this shop is
[Instant get-satisfactioner
who keeps saying cute things to himself]
in front of my place.
[The8 is lying on the bed] [Amazed]
Wow!
Wow, it's so awesome!
[Satisfied by the bed]
This is so nice.
What's this?
[Tempting offer 1]
May I try this?
It feels like...
[The8's how to shop
- Trying everything in display]
[My hips, hold on]
My hips are moving continuously.
[What's the next thing?]
[Massage chairs]
I like it.
[Tempting offer 2]
What's this?
Does she want me to try this?
How?
[Sales reps are enthusiastic]
What's this?
[Finished experience of
a mysterious device]
[The8's how to shop -
Experiences everything displayed in the shop]
[But never buys if it's not necessary]
They have many health products.
[ - Active but careful get-satisfactioner]
[Meanwhile]
What?
We can control this.
[Isn't it cool?]
We can control this robot.
- This looks fun.
- Right.
It's small like this.
[Loving it]
It moves.
It looks interesting.
[May I buy one?]
- Get one. - May I?
- How much?
- Those around me persuade.
[What?]
It's around 180,000 won.
[Please tell me to buy]
- May I? - Sorry?
If you like it, buy one.
If you don't, leave it.
Do you want me to
play rock paper scissors?
If you win, you will buy.
If I win, you won't buy.
[Strange way to decide a purchase]
Nobody knows the result.
Rock paper scissors!
[So cool]
- Buy! - Yes!
[Vernon's how to shop
- Shopper-holic who buys something he likes]
[Bold get-satisfactioner who
invests things he like without hesitation]
[Four get-satisfactioners
have different tastes]
[The entire episode of "It" item
shopping will air on Naver TV]
[Vernon is ready for a test run]
- Can it reach here? - Yes.
[Confident eyes]
Sure, it can travel as far as 30m.
[Proud of it]
- Pride. - He's so proud of it.
I thought he invented it.
[Amazing]
Send it to me!
[Vernon's "It" item from Japan]
Doesn't it make any expression?
No expression?
[My type]
But it's so cute. Just cute.
[Loving eyes for the robot]
- A good purchase.
- It is well-made. Look.
This is a magnetic part.
[Get-satisfactioner's pride]
- Right! - Look.
[Explaining why it's so precious]
It has the balancing part
so it can strike a balance
wherever it goes.
[Like a dad who boasts his child]
It can move all alone.
Wow.
[That's nice]
It looks fun.
[Recognition for a get-satisfactioner]
- A great job.
- A nice purchase.
He's so satisfied with this.
I'm so satisfied with it
and happy about it.
[Live long happily with Vernon]
[Jun's "It" item]
And Jun?
I like plums.
- But it's hard to get plums in Korea.
- Right.
So I bought a lot of
plums in Japan.
[Plums' current location: Jun's stomach]
But I ate them up.
[You may do that]
Right, you may have eaten them up.
[Jun liked snacks in Japan]
I saw amazing snacks in Japan.
You like snacks.
He likes jelly. Especially,
[Hoshi's testimony]
he likes the milk tea drink.
[1 per a day]
- He drinks one per day.
- He loves it!
[Jun's roommate?]
Who does Jun share his room?
Seungkwan and Dino.
[Paradise of snacks?]
I guess your room is full of snacks.
[Sniper]
But Jun does not offer snacks to us.
[Frozen]
So you didn't steal them?
[Snacks in a fridge]
Right, I put Chinese snacks in the fridge
and they ate those crazily...
[Excuse me?]
What? Hey!
[Laughing out loud]
I saw they ate secretly.
[Mispronunciation]
- Secretly. - Secretly.
[Professional MC]
He didn't pronounce s from secretly.
[He's laughing so hard]
[Please move on]
They ate secretly.
[Joshua's "It" item]
- And you, Joshua? - These days,
[Calming]
it's hard to see stars at night.
[Star light projector]
So I wanted to buy this.
Because we can't see stars at night.
So I bought this astro star lamp.
[On]
- When I turn this on, - Then?
The light...
Stars...
[Joshua sent this video clip]
Insert it into this.
Then, let's turn off the light.
[The ceiling is full of stars]
Amazing! Stars on the ceiling!
This would be nice.
[Good night, Joshua]
You can enjoy stars on the ceiling.
Stars come out.
[Amazing]
You can adjust it.
- How...
- Even zodiac signs?
[Of course]
Using this one.
[Joshua's zodiac sign]
I'm Capricorn.
[Insert a Capricon tool]
- There? - Yes, you can insert yours.
Then, put it in the middle.
[Like a science teacher]
You can see your zodiac sign.
[Minimalist Joshua]
When we started shooting this show,
Joshua raised his hand
to say he rarely shops.
[Silence]
He's never talked for an hour and a half.
I thought about talking to him,
because he was so silent.
I wanted to ask if
he's not interested in shopping at all.
[Joshua's wish list]
- But he has that on his list.
- I wanted to buy this.
Seungkwan used
[Seungkwan's mood lamp]
- Stars... - A mood lamp.
- He turned on the lamp.
I saw that
[Unexpected twist] [Sorry?]
and wanted to buy a better one.
[Sudden disrespectful comment]
[Still wondering]
[Bring your ear to me!]
- After seeing his,
- It's hilarious.
[One more time]
I thought I should buy a better one.
[Arrogant]
- When he goes to the jungles,
- In jungles...
he will realize it's not necessary.
[Biting teeth]
Stars are amazing in the jungle.
Really.
[Ignoring]
I wanted to see stars.
["It" item for Joshua who loves stars]
[Star light projector]
[The8's "It" item?]
The8, what did you bring?
- What's that?
- An overall that we doodled.
[Overall]
- An overall. - An outfit.
I bought this one.
There's no pattern or print on it.
[Behind-the-scene story]
- It has no print. - No.
I wanted to draw a painting on this.
When I visited a practice room,
I suggested members
should draw things on it.
So I asked them.
I asked them to draw things freely.
I will wear this
on my way to the airport.
[Right]
All the members joined.
Freely.
[Made by SEVENTEEN]
Members drew these.
This overall didn't matter to me
but the drawings are so precious.
[One of a kind]
- This is the only one in the world.
- Right.
[A real "It" item that has meaning]
It's so precious.
I keep it well.
- Touching.
- This is the real "It" item.
That's one of a kind.
[The8 did this using paint]
I drew this using paint.
[Praises]
- I think he did a great job! - Using paint...
[Precious]
I will see this to remember members.
[SEVENTEEN's memories from the outfit]
- I will remember them. - Right.
- It will be a good reminder.
- Meaningful.
Thanks for sharing your
precious items and belongings.
Put it down, please.
[Strong-willed Wonwoo]
I see.
[Respect your preference]
I see how much you like it.
I respect your taste!
[Everything boiled down to a tracksuit]
It's the only thing I remember!
- He can't sleep tonight.
- Did you see that?
[Smiling]
He did this to me.
[Laughing out loud]
[Please put it aside]
Asking for recognition. I see.
[Smiling]
I admit.
As we admit,
don't worry.
[Like Puss in Boots]
He looked at me like a kitten.
I was surprised to see him.
[SVT's second keyword "Get-satisfactioner]
We talked about get-satisfactioners.
[Time to see the "It" items
of people in their 20s]
I realized young people in their 20s
has their own special items
that suit your own taste.
I realized you guys have
various tastes.
[Get-satisfactioners who spend
for his or her own satisfaction]
Young people.
I came to understand
what young generations like.
This was a nice chance to
get to know about you and youngsters.
[How do you feel?]
How do you feel about the 2nd session?
I liked everything
others have shown.
Each one's "It" item
[Presenting it]
was amazing.
[A gift for you]
I think they have their own taste.
[Surprised]
[No thank you]
Except for yours. Kidding.
[Meaningful]
Those were meaningful to them.
I enjoyed this session a lot.
[Through "It" items]
It helped us to know more about members.
As I saw shopping styles of
others who I've never shopped together,
I want to go shopping together.
[Leader wants to shop with members]
I saw their shopping style now
and I want to enjoy
shopping together with them.
[There are various types of get-satisfactioners]
I think that's a nice idea.
As you came to know
there are many ways,
[You can help each other
for satisfactory purchase]
You can discuss together
to enjoy shopping.
I think this session was nice.
I had a great time
while talking with you.
[Shopping is the act to find your identity]
Thank you.
[And refine your identity
- Thomas Hine]
[A fairy for ending]
[Please check out behind-the-scene
video clips on Naver TV, April 13 8 PM]
[What do youngsters hate?]
What are the things that you don't like?
- Seungkwan?
- He's mean.
[Laughing out loud]
- Freedom to hate. - Freedom to dislike.
- Today's keyword is the freedom to hate.
I don't like walking around outside.
[Likes to stay home]
I go outside only for special occasions.
[Legendary LieV]
How can we respect
such a special preference?
[SEVENTEEN's different taste]
Seungkawn likes kids.
- Jeonghan likes...
- I like kids.
[But it's too hard to be with them]
I liked them but it was hard...
[Smile like a dad]
[Dear kids]
[Trying to interact]
Come here. Come on.
[Who am I? Where am I?]
Breaking news for you.
Someone sent a message
to reveal the truth
about SEVENTEEN's dorm.
[Anonymous informer]
I hope they live like decent human beings.
Nobody would recognize who I am, right?
[Trying to figure out who it is]
Who is it?
[Claiming innocent]
It's you!
It's not me.
[If you're curious,
please watch it on Mnet!]