Claire:Previously...
Colum doesna travel,
So visiting the
tenants and tacksmen
That can't come
to the gathering,
That falls to me.
Have you seen any of
your scottish companions
Raise funds
for the rebellion?
Let's get on with it.
Randall:Why would
dougal mackenzie
Rather adopt you
as one of his own
Than allow me
to question you?
I was wondering
if you had a potion
That might open
a lad's heart
to a lassie.
What's his name?
Horrocks.
There's a chance
to get the price
lifted from my head.
A redcoat deserter.
Claims he was there,
Saw who actually
killed the sergeant.
Claire:I knew where
we were going
without having to ask,
The province of a man
I unfortunately
knew all too well.
I'll thank ye to take
your hands off my wife.
Dougal:
Where's your mind, lad?
Horrocks is waiting.
Already washed the dust from your throat
Mr. Horrocks?
It would be wise if you told us what happened
that night in Fort William.
Did you or did you not tell Hugh Monroe,
you saw who shot the Sergeant?
I did.
Forgive me, but I...
I haven't tasted
fine whiskey like that in quite some time.
I  can use another wee nip.
I look forward,
I'm anxious,
That you name the person who committed the crime
I was falsely accused of.
Have you the gold Hugh
Monroe promised to pay?
Yes.
Then hand it over
and we'll move on with the deal.
The name, first.
You'll have it when I have the gold in my hand.
Well that was the understanding
Give him the gold.
I trust his word.
The british army
trusted him, too.
Perhaps today's not
such a good day
for business after all.
Whether you deserted
is no concern of ours,
mr. Horrocks.
We commend ye for it.
I've come a long way,
At considerable
danger to myself,
Eluding redcoat patrols...
(speaking other language)
The man who shot the sergeant
Was captain Jonathan Randall
himself.
Ye expect us to believe
that a captain,
Even one as vile
as black jack,
Would shoot his own man?
You know randall.
I suppose he can answer that.
I canna use randall's
name to clear my own.
You bargained for a name.
A name is what you received.
Good day, lads.
Let him go.
Man:Jamie!
Jamie!
Claire.
I was minding her,
I swear.
I went for a piss and...
Where is she?
She must've wandered off,
and when I caught up,
The redcoats had her.
She was fighting
and thrashing about,
But they took her.
They were headed south.
Hold on, Fort William?
I know what's on your mind boy,
but what you're thinking is impossible.
I'm going with or without you!
Then Dougal and I must abstain from
any open action
against the British garrison.
If we were captured,  then the  consequences
upon the clan and Colum ...
No...
the risks are too great, I'm afraid.
Any man wants to ride with you
I'll not stop 'em.
I'm not beseachin'
anyone for help.
But I'm also not
proud to refuse.
I'll go with you.
I'm not doing
nothing special today...
- but a wee ride might be
amusing.
Sure, but our conditions
you will have to heed.
♪ Sing me a song of a lass that is gone
♪ Say, could that lass be I?
♪ Merry of soul she sailed on a dais
♪ Over the sea to Skye
♪ Billow and breeze, islands and seas
♪ Mountains of rain and sun
♪ All that was good,
all that was fair
♪ All that was me is gone
♪ Sing me a song of a lass that is gone
♪ Say, could that lass be I?
♪ Merry of soul she sailed on a dais
♪ Over the sea...
♪ ... to Skye
Where is the englishwoman?
I don't know who you mean.
My friend here isna a bit
pleased with yer answer.
Pray, I don't know.
Pray that you do.
Or your next words'll be
in a lassie's voice.
The commander's office.
In the tower.
Thank you.
(bird calling signal)
Murtagh, don't ye
wait too long.
Claire:Help!
I'll thank ye to take
your hands off my wife.
Good god.
(laughs)
Dougal mackenzie
neglected to mention
That you married
the stripe-backed thief.
How's my handiwork
looking these days?
Very well,
Despite your efforts.
I don't suppose
you'd show me?
Be the last thing
you ever saw.
Oh.
Only risk brings
the possibility
of reward, hmm?
Just shoot this
bastard, jamie.
(screams)
Do. Shoot me.
Shoot us both.
And alarm the entire fort
of your presence.
Oh.
It appears we're to have
an audience, madam.
I think we should endeavor
to enjoy ourselves.
I certainly shall.
Now, put that pistol
on the table
And let us commence
with the evening's
entertainment.
Do it.
Slowly.
I will slit her throat,
I swear to god.
Slowly.
That wasn't too hard.
Back you go.
Do it!
Get out of here, jamie.
Just go. Go!
Everyone, keep calm.
(whimpers)
Easy does it.
(laughs)
Oh, first she orders
you to fire,
Now she orders
you to flee.
Who is the man
in this marriage, fraser?
I will cut off
your balls, I swear.
You are
a foul-mouthed scold.
For the life of me,
I cannot understand
why any man
would pledge himself
To a woman.
Especially such
a mendacious slut
as this one.
Would you like
your husband
to join us maybe?
What do you say,
fraser, hmm?
Huh?
Or would you
prefer to watch?
You bluffed your way
in here with
an empty pistol.
Ned said not to kill anyone,
So I had all the
weapons unloaded.
This way.
Wait.
Up here.
You are sure
there's water down there,
aren't you?
Aye. I think so.
Still a couple hours' ride
from the drover
We should
water the horses.
Give him a drink of water,
please?
Aye.
Are you all right?
Randall,
he didn't hurt you?
No, He didn't have time,
thanks to you.
I'm waiting for you
to say something.
Anything that approaches
an apology.
An apology?
I was taken hostage
by jack randall.
Are you trying to say
that's somehow my fault?
Well, it is your fault.
Had you stayed put where I ordered you to stay,
None of this would have happened.
Yeah, but no.
Ye won't listen to me,
Why mind me,
I am not but yer husband.
Ye take it into yer mind
to do as ye damn please
I find ye flat on yer back
with yer skirts up,
And the worst scum
of the land
between your legs,
About to take you
before my very eyes.
I begged you
to take me with you.
And I told you
there was no danger
in me going along.
Would you
listen to me? No.
No, I'm just a woman.
No, why should you
pay any attention
to what I have to say?
Women are only fit
to do as they're told
and obey orders.
If ye'd done that,
we wouldn't be on
the run now With a hundred redcoats
on our tail.
Try that again
and I'll slap you
until yer ears ring.
You're a brute and a fool!
Do you think I went and got
Captured by the english on purpose?
Aye! I do think
ye did it on purpose
To get back at me
for what happened
at the glade.
At the glade?
With the British deserters?
You think, to punish you,
I went for a walk
in the woods
On the chance that some
British soldiers would be going by?
Christ, jamie, I went for a walk!
I ordered you to stay put!
I don't have to do
what you tell me to.
Aye, you do.
You are my wife.
Oh, your wife?
Your wife.
You think
I'm your property,
don't you?
You think I belong to you
and you can't stand
For someone to have
something else
that belongs to you.
You do belong to me
and you are my wife,
Whether you
like it or not.
Well, I don't like it!
I don't like it one bit!
That doesn't matter
to you either, does it?
And as long as
I'm there to
warm your bed,
You don't care
what I think
or how I feel!
That's all a wife is to you.
Something to stick
your cock into
whenever you feel the urge.
Let go of me,
you fucking bastard!
You foul-mouthed bitch!
You'll not speak
to me that way!
I went to you
at fort william
Armed with an empty pistol
and my bare hands.
When you screamed...
You're tearing
my guts out, claire.
I'm sorry.
Jamie ...
Forgive me.
Forgiven.
I'm sorry, too.
I'll ask your pardon
for what I said.
I was sore
and I said more
than I meant.
Will ye forgive me, too?
Forgiven.
Jamie:  She asked forgiveness
and I gave it.
But the truth is,
I'd forgiven everything
she'd done
And everything she could do,
long before that day.
For me,
that was no choice.
That was falling in love.
Looks like we'll be needing
a few more plates, then.
So, while murtagh was
Setting the fuses on the gunpowder,
I sent three of
the bloody jessies
to meet the almighty.
I'm not hearing this.
When I heard the explosion,
I thought the
walls of the fort
would come down.
Did ye use yer breath
or yer farts to subdue them?
Are you calling me a liar?
Aye, because ye are lying.
Ye killed nobody.
Oh, oh.
For god's sake, angus!
Sit down..
..stop flapping yer gums.. Use it for
something useful for a change.
Man: I'm not gonna
tell anything if you're taking that tone.
I don't believe
I've properly
thanked all of you.
-For what you did last night.
Ned, have ye got any wine down there?
Ned: Yeah, well,
they do actually
have some rhenish.
Quite nice, if I may say.
It's been a long day.
I'll go upstairs.
She doesna understand
what she nearly cost us.
Aye.
And she needs to.
Think they'll ever
speak to me again?
Aye.
They will.
Come to bed, Jamie.
I'm afraid we've a matter
Still to settle between us
Before we sleep tonight.
What is it?
If a man among us
had put the rest in danger,
As you did,
He would have likely had
his ears cropped, or been flogged,
If not killed outright.
I didn't know.
Good...
Well, I ken you're not yet
familiar with our ways,
And that's some excuse.
Still, I did tell ye
to stay hid.
And if ye'd done so,
none of this would
have happened.
Now, the british
will be looking
high and low for us.
As for captain randall...
Well, that's
something else again.
He'll be looking for you,
Especially now that
he knows you're here.
Aye.
He...
It's personal for him.
I am so sorry, jamie.
If it were just me
ye'd hurt by it,
I wouldna
say more about it.
But your actions
put all the men
in jeopardy.
Right...
...best get on with it.
Ye've done
considerable damage
disobeying my orders,
And I'm gonna
punish ye for it.
What do you mean?
Oh, you know
fine well what I mean.
Now, get down
by the bed and
lift yer shift, lass.
I'll do no such thing.
Now, claire...
I have said I'm sorry.
And I am.
And I will never do
such a thing again.
That's just the point.
You might.
Ye come from a place
where things are easier,
I think.
Where it's not a matter
of life and death
If you disobey orders
or take matters into
your own hands.
But it's the hard truth
in places and times
like these that
A light action can have...
...very serious
consequences.
All right.
You're right, of course.
I will obey your orders,
even if I don't
agree with them.
Good.
Now then, get off the bed
and we'll get this over with.
What?
I said I would follow your orders.
There's a difference between
understanding something
in yer mind
And really knowing it,
deep down.
I can tell ye from
my own experience
That a good hiding
makes ye understand things
In a more serious light.
But as I said,
if it was just me
you put in danger...
But it wasn't.
There's such a thing
as justice, claire.
You've done wrong
to all the men,
And you must suffer for it.
I'm yer husband.
It's my duty to attend to it.
- I will not let you beat me!
You won't?
I doubt you'll have
much to say about it.
The lad's getting on with it.
Seems so.
That is his duty.
You're my wife, like it or not.
I'll scream!
Well, likely,
if not before,
certainly during!
I expect they'll hear ye
in the next village.
Ye've got good lungs.
This'll go faster
if ye just yield, woman.
I'm gonna make you suffer!
Oh!
Well, ye already are.
You're taking
pleasure in this,
you barbarian!
Sounds like holy hell up there.
I'm not sure who's punishing who.
I'll never forgive you!
If I can forgive ye
for what you did,
You can forgive me, too,
As soon as ye can
sit down again.
You sadist!
I dinna ken, what's a sadist?
As for my pleasure,
I said I was gonna punish you.
No!
I didna say I wasna
gonna enjoy it.
I hope that jamie
wasn't too harsh on
ye last night?
A skelped arse never did anyone
permanent damage.
Looks like she gave
as good as she got.
Ah, well, it might not be permanent,
but it hurts like hell.
She'll not make
that mistake again.
Indeed. Yes.
Come and have
a seat here
next to me, lassie.
No, thank you,
I'll stand.
Over there.
Ah, it is good to be home.
In the loving bosom of those who hold us dear.
There's no one about.
I do not know about you lot,
but I'm starving!
Go after her boy,
I'll keep to the mounts
.
Sassenach.
Claire.
I prefer not to fall behind
my wife.
Then walk faster.
Welcome home, my dears.
It seems like yesterday that you ran
kitchen by steal food.
- And now you've gone and married ...
- Leave him be..
Fussin' over him like that...
He'll be no use to anyone...
Me especially.
You are comin'  back to the stables,
work with horses.
Aye.
Congratulations to you both.
I look forward to hearing
all about yer nuptials.
It's been some time
since we've had
a wedding here.
My profound good wishes
For a long and happy
marriage,
Lady Broch Tuarach.
I did not enjoy that one bit.
Did you not notice the look
Colum gave me?
It seemed friendly
enough for me.
Do not drink anything ...
He did not offer a single toast,
in our honor.
What do I know about
clans of manners ?!
Did not you see?
He does not approve of this marriage.
He is not alone.
What the hell do you mean by such?
Will you not answer me, Claire?
I know what that means!
Happiness is (...).
Who said that?
Me.
Just now.
Yes.
Love.
It is not a simple matter.
It is like...
try to plan for every season
from one moment to the next
And when you
ready for the sun.
The ice comes.
What do you know that?
More than you think you ignorant putz.
You mean my mother?
I am a hard man,
Ellen knew it.
Your father had a gentle side.
I thought it was a weakness.
I was wrong.
And by the time  I realized that ...
your parents had pledged
themselves to one another.
What's done is done, lad.
What do you do next that matters.
Colum awaits you
in his chambers.
Tell him I'm on my way.
Pardon.
Why did you do it?
I waited for you, Jamie.
I was counting the days
till you'd return.
I had no notion
about yerself and...
It wasna
something I planned.
Then why?
Why did you do it?
'twas Dougal's
arrangement, ye see.
It's no simple story,
I can tell ye that much.
But an explanation
will have to wait.
Colum summons me.
I must go.
Aye.
Ye canna keep
a Mackenzie waiting.
But we'll speak again.
Aye, you have my word.
Ah. 'tis the bridegroom.
Aye.
Now that I have
all three of you weasels
gathered together,
Who would like to explain
Fort William?
Is clan Mackenzie
going to have to answer
for yer little raid, hmm?
No.
Any repercussions
will land solely on me.
Captain Randall
will make sure of that.
Fine.
Now, back to the rents.
As I say, it has been
a lean year for
for some of the tenants,
But we have
much of the stock
still to sell off,
which should help the
balance the scales.
What about
the other money
you collected?
The money for
the bonnie Stuart prince Across the water, hmm?
'tis for the Jacobites,
is it not?
Did ye not think that
one among the rent party
Would remain
loyal to his laird?
Or at least,
young Jamie, here,
He does me the honor
of looking fittingly guilty.
You mistake
concern for guilt.
My conscience is clear.
I owe no loyalty to
Charlie or James.
He speaks truth, brother.
We merely used
the welts on his back
to illustrate
British justice.
We raised that
gold honorably.
We never concealed
the fact from anybody
That we were
raising money
to restore
The rightful king
to his throne.
That, I might remind ye,
Is a cause more important
than any clan or man.
Is that so?
Well, this clan remains
under the charge of this man.
It is still my pleasure To choose
what causes
are supported.
And the
clan Mackenzie's welfare
Comes before
any king or country.
I've proved
my loyalty to you
time and again.
I've collected your rents, I've fought your battles,
I've protected yer person
For the love of Christ, I've even assured
your bloodline!
Now, I think that such fealty is
worth a mere bag of gold,
Don't you?
Leave my sight.
I shall try to
calm his distemper.
Either that
or I will calm it for him.
Perhaps you'd rather
chastise me at a later time?
Stay.
I opened my home to you
as sanctuary from the British.
I gave my food,
I gave my hospitality.
Even when you refused
to pledge fealty to me,
I continued to
grant ye quarter
and protection.
And how am I recompensed?
You marry a Sassenach,
Knowing well enough
that none in the clan
Will support ye now
as my successor.
I meant no such
betrayal, uncle.
And it will be given you to
opportunity to prove it.
What do you want me to do?
My brother must never
be allowed to succeed me,
as chief of MacKenzies.
Do you not agree?
Dougal has,
a fiery temper that
can not be easily ...
Say no more.
I have seen we are in agreement.
I have his replacement
still in mind.
He stands before me.
But...
But you...
You already declared,
that my marriage precludes me from that honor.
For the time being....
A marriage of convenience.
I do not understand
the meaning...
But this is not England.
Life here can be perilous.
For whom exactly?
I mentioned no one in particular.
Well, for a moment I ...
I was afraid you were speaking about my wife.
And if so...
I will be forced to take
that as a threat.
Of course you would.
That is the precise mind of a chief.
Claire: I knew it.
That first time I saw Dougal and hamish
Playing together in the courtyard.
Aye.
Many have gossiped
about it in whispers,
And every one of us
in the room
already kent it well.
But that's the first time
I've ever heard
Dougal proclaim
he's Hamish's father.
Thought Colum was going to
run him through right there.
That would solve
a few problems.
Aye, if the storm
canna be calmed
between the brothers,
I'll be the one
to pay the price.
It's hardly the first time
he and Dougal Have been at odds,
god knows.
I'm sure it'll be fine
in the morning.
Aye.
What are you doing?
- I thought ...
- Think again.
(...) it's not your business.
My sweet angel.
You can come out now.
Jamie Fraser.
I thought I was hid
well enough.
T'was your smell
that gave you away.
A man's sweat.
Couldn't be Arthur.
He's too prissy to ever work up a good lather
Yes well...
He holds a postion that does not require much labor.
He doesn't do much laboring in any position.
Hmmph!
I saw your new bride.
Earlier
Don't worry Jamie.
She'll recover.
Despite you beating her.
Claire is a strong woman.
But if you ever tan her hide again.
Or ruined her heart.
You'd amazed,
What my concoctions can do to a body.
It would be a shame...
To ruin such a pretty package.
Your husband was right.
You should mind to your own affairs.
Dougal tells ye something,
it's as if it's law.
It is nice reminding you that.
Devil, man.
He's just a lad.
His mouth has been in Colum's ear
And his lips half up his arse!
He gave Colum the moneys
collected for the Jacobites.
And it wasna his to give.
It wasna Colum's to take.
The Mackenzie
ordered me to do it!
I was just serving my oath
to himself as given!
Or would you have me
lie to the laird?
If the Mackenzie
asked you the same, You'd do it,
would you not?
Not after what
he did to Dougal, no.
And what about you, Jamie?
Where does your loyalty lie
Between the chief
and the war chief?
Now, there is but one laird
of the clan, is there not?
Enough of this blather.
The issue needs no debate.
The lad shoulda come to us
For counsel afore taking action.
For his disobedience,
He's getting the due
course of punishment.
Besides,
this is Mackenzie
business.
You, Frasers, should
mind to yer own.
Now, stand aside and let us get back to ours.
Hey.
What's all this, then?
I thought we were
hunting stag?
Aye.
Who's with me?
I ken I'd find you here.
This has been your secret place
since ye were a lad.
Not so secret
if you find me so easily.
You promised we would speak.
Aye,
I remember the first time
I saw you, James Fraser,
Comin' through
the gates of Leoch.
It was only seven years old,
still a child.
You didn't notice back then..
..how my heart lept when you were near.
..and you went away, all those years.
I never forgot you.
I'm wed now.
And 'twas
a gallant thing ye did.
Marrying the Sassenach
to spare her from the british.
'tis true the marriage
was Dougal's
arrangement, but...
You dinna look...
very happy.
Ye look like
ye're carrying the
world on yer back.
- Laoghaire ...
- When you returned ...
When you took the beating
for me in the great hall,
I knew I wasn't wrong.
That you felt the same.
And then,
that day in the alcove ...
The way you kissed me.
She was married before.
But I've lain with no one.
I want ye
to be the first
And only one to have me.
No.
I made a vow
and I'll not break it.
Even for a lass
as bonnie as you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
- Where is Dougal?
-
How do you stop
two dogs from fightin'?
Bastard!
It's over!
No! No!
drink as friends?
Murtagh, get these good lads some whiskey!
You settled that scirmash like
a future leader of the MacKenzies.
There's a reason you're not know for your sense of humor.
Well if it's plain talk you're after...
Here's something you could chew off.
It's getting a wee bit uncomfortable
around  here
for my taste.
Rupert's right.
This is not our fight.
I'll saddle the horses.
Ye take hold of Claire
And we'll be away
from here this very night.
And how would we live?
Horrocks was
my best chance,
And now,
I may be even
an outlaw for good.
We'll live off the land.
Or has castle life
made ye soft?
Would ye have me sleeping under a tree
Come winter with my wife?
Leave her, then.
We can send for the lass
when we find safe beds.
Aye, spoken like
the unwed man ye are.
For pity's sake, Jamie,
It's either up tail and away,
or we stay and pick a side.
It's not like Colum's
gonna give
Dougal back the gold.
Not that I see
that it matters much
either way.
The bonnie prince
isna sailing from
Italy anytime soon.
No,
He isna, is he?
Peace, you say? Peace?
You come here and tell me
That clansman brawls
with clansman!
That my own brother
defies me.
How can there be peace
until such disloyalty
is punished?
Well, chastising the guilty
might sooth yer anger,
But I doubt
it will accomplish
anything more.
The bad blood will only fester,
leading to more violence,
Until the clan explodes
into open warfare.
What would you have me do?
Make yer brother a gift
of the Jacobite gold.
You'd have me commit
treason to the crown?
Sanctiona stuart restoration
to the throne?
A stuart restoration
is but an airy hope,
my laird.
There is no Jacobite army.
The highland clans are too busy reiving
each other's cattle
To even consider uniting.
While bonnie prince charlie
lounges idly,
Being pampered
by the pope.
Aye. Aye, all that is true.
Meanwhile, my own clan teeters
on the brink of civil war.
Then remove the source
of the immediate conflict.
Give Dougal back the gold
And ye pacify him
and his companions.
Let yer brother
play the rebel,
As long as
he does it quietly.
Let him whisper
of a free Scotland for now,
While you bide your time
And wait to see
how events transpire.
If bonnie prince charlie
ever returns with
a call to arms,
You can decide then
which side to back.
Dougal may be war chief,
But he knows only you
can cry for war.
Bring my brother
and Ned Gowan here.
Are we to
stand here all day,
Or is there a purpose
to this summons?
One day, brother,
You'll talk your
head off your shoulders
And right onto a pike.
A month ago,
You swore an oath
to me on this dirk.
Ye recall?
Aye.
So tell me, brother,
What's a man's
word worth these days?
A bag of gold, perhaps?
My oath to youis an oath to
Scotland.
I've not broken it,
nor will I ever.
We'll see.
Go on, then.
Play the rebel.
See where it leads ye.
I thank you, brother.
Ned, send a missiveto the
Duke of Sandringham,
Inviting him
to a banquet
in his honor.
Best warn the men of the household
To keep their arses out of his reach.
Sweet christ, man, Can ye not keep
that tongue of yers From wagging?
Very wise, laird, To get the measure
of the Jacobite cause
From an Englishman's
perspective.
It will take more
than yer approval
To get back
in my good graces,
ned gowan.
Get out of my sight,
all three of you.
Colum and Dougal have mended fences.
It's not worth it.
It is best to leave them alone.
There are no shortage of Highlanders at Leoch.
That's not the company I crave last week as well
Our lives in the Highlands
are steeped in traditions
customs and rituals.
So I've seen.
And Colum chose
to risk looking weak,
Publicly changing
his position,
Because peace was
more important
than custom.
I saw a rigid man bend.
It made me mindful.
About what?
Wives obey their husbands.
Husbands discipline them
when they don't.
Well, that's how
it was with my father,
And his father and on
and on and on back.
But maybe, for you and me,
it has to go a different way.
I swear on the cross
of my lord jesus,
And by the holy iron
which I hold
That I give you my fealty
and pledge you my loyalty.
If ever my hand is raised
In rebellion against you again,
I pray that this holy iron
Might pierce my heart.
Is it not enough, Claire?
Do you not
want me anymore?
Do you wish to
live separately?
Well, that's what
I should want...
But I don't.
The key to Lallybroch.
What?
Yer ring.
I had the blacksmith Fashion your ring
from my key.
Why didn't you tell me that before,
When you gave it to me?
I wanted to wait
until I took ye back
to lallybroch.
So ye'd know the place
was as much yours as mine.
But now, I dinna
ken when, if ever,
we'll get back there.
Jamie, I...
And that...
That thought
does not pain me
As much as it
once might have.
It is my home now.
I want you, Claire.
I love you so much
I can hardly breathe.
Will ye have me?
Yes. Yes, I'll have you.
Listen to me.
If you ever raise
a hand to me again,
James Fraser,
I will cut your heart out
and have it for breakfast.
Do you understand me?
Do you?
You have my word.
You're mine.
Mo nighean donn.
Mine, now and forever.
And I mean to make you
call me master.
I am your master
and you're mine.
It seems that I can not
possess your soul
without losing my own.
Sassenach.
Yes, master?
What does "fucking" mean?
- What?
"fucking."
After Fort William
you called me
a "fucking bastard".
Well, that means
what we just did..
What about "sadist"?
Ye called me that as well.
Well, that means someone
Who takes sexual pleasure
in hurting someone.
Oh, well.
Ye dinna flatter me overmuch,
But I canna fault
yer observations.
Um...
Oh. Was I too rough on you?
Well, If you bed a vixen,
you have to expect to get bit.
Come here and
bite me some more.
I'm ravenous.
Hmm. So am I.
You meant food.
Mmm-hmm.
I'll go to the kitchen,
fetch us something to eat.
What on earth is this?
Where'd ye get that?
- It was just there.
What's wrong?
What is it?
It's an ill-wish.
Which is?
It's meant to bring
pain or harm
or even death.
Who would put
such a thing
under our bed?
Jamie?
Laoghaire.